

# Javier Borbolla Ureña

Fullstack developer

## Contact



636 78 80 93



jebx.dev



javierbuinfo@gmail.com

# **Idioms**

Spanish - Native English - B2

# Languages

Js Javascript	4 years
NodeJS NodeJS	4 years
😇 HTML5	4 years
₹ CSS3	4 years
React	4 years
Python	2 years
<b>◎</b> C#	2 years
	2 years
Ts Typescript	+1 year
<i>₿</i> Redux	+1 year
MongoDB	+1 year
Solidity	+1 year
<sup>™</sup> PHP	+1 year
MySQL	+1 year

+20 technologies, libraries and frameworks that could be interested in my website

https://jebx.dev

#### About me

Self-taught programmer for 6 years. Passionate about learning new techniques and languages. Actually, focused in **MERN stack**. Whenever I can, I try to optimize and automate all the processes that are in my hand. My hobby is programming everything I can think of and I have a high capacity for analysis and problem solving.

#### **Education**

### Certificated in deep learning & CUDA

2021-2021 - University of Malaga

#### Expert in reverse engine and malware intelligence

2021-2021 - University of Malaga

#### **Cybersecurity master**

2020-2021 - Valencian International University

#### **Web Application Development**

2017-2019 - High School Severo Ochoa

#### Microcomputer systems and networks

2015-2017 - High School Severo Ochoa

### **Professional Experience**

#### //FRONTEND DEVELOPER AND BUG FIXER

2023 - Present, Copernicus S.L.

Develop and maintenance of the internal web application with **React and Typescript.** Daily and weekly coordinance with the entire team. Daily use of **Git.** 

### //SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2018 - Present On (Time)

- -Skyminers / React, NextJS, NodeJS, Solidity
- -Wildprint S.L. / React, Firebase, Tailwind
- -Krebor Technology S.L. / React, Firebase, Tailwind, Typescript
- -Jebx.dev / React, Firebase, Tailwind, Vite, Typescript
- -A.M.P.A / PHP, Wordpress
- -Krebor Technology S.L. / C#, SQLite, WPF

4 years of personal and autonomous development. Knowledge in more than 35 technologies, languages and frameworks. Good practices, use of interfaces, classes, enums, etc.. Knowledge in **git, jira**, **SOLID principles, hexagonal architecture**. Habituated to do **sprints** and follow the **Scrum** process. Fullstack develop with **MERN stack** tendency. Passionate about find bugs and optimize everything. I have do the entire develop of +10 websites and writed a lot of scripts and bots. Facility with **requests manage**, **sessions**, **JSONs**, **sockets**, **async functions and multithreading**. I have analyzed malware and i know obfuscation techniques

#### //FRONTEND DEVELOPER AND BUG FIXER

2022 - 2022, NTT DATA - Jazztel

Develop and maintenance of the Jazztel's Website with **Angular and NodeJS.** Daily and weekly coordinance with some teams and direct interlocution with the client. Daily use of **Jenkins, Jira and Git.** In addition, i was mandated to find and solve bugs in the testing servers.

#### //FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2020 - 2020, MBVR

I was head of frontend development for a startup related to security against Covid-19. Development started with **C# and Blazor** but we ended up migrating to **C# and React (Redux + SemanticUI)**. Weekly meetings with the back team. I was also in charge of adding security to the network and to the intraconnections (**JWT, encryption, etc.**).

#### //RPA SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2019 - 2019, Accenture - Movistar

Development and improvement of Movistar's internal software. Use of **Blueprism** to automate the processes carried out by the customer service team and in stores. I improved some of these softwares by performing **web scrapping** with the use of **HTTP requests** and thus optimizing the execution speed x5.